So today I am bringing a new block, so
this is done and I have taken the block color, timing chain,
etc. Everything, so you guys keep doing it
and I have a small family in my YouTube,
this is the biggest one, this pimples are increasing,
so keep doing it on such app lock and in such a situation I will
bring videos for you guys and if you like it then
please like, comment and share that
today we will see this entrance app, you
can grow, you have one and with chain there is
no work done here and this is done,
N president ward number is
more than 60,
eyes were inside the block, we got it, so take it out,
this is done and drop popular,
I opened it first because the video will become
too long, so I should keep it
open first, it is Agro's blog, so
check its partner, the number is 2010 1598 liters,
I will find it inside it,
you guys will find it standing in it,
okay and this is the stunt scene,
if you still say, there is
a box with it, it is locked and this is made of
steel  This is Gas Cat, this is Blockbuster,
okay, so let's see the Android tax rate for the common people,
how much has it happened, so the end drop which is the
rate price of the block is Ward
No. 23 of
2020,
2015, this entire family
to family
subscription
from 3000 to 3000,
how does the timing change of Aishwarya enter
affect this, it is not open
because the game is very late, so if I am a fan, then if I get to be
in the video, then you guys comment, I will
definitely
bring a video for you guys in the next turn, okay, and if you comment, then
I will give it at the lowest price, but
you guys do not get time to replay by commenting, so
I am
not able to reply to any such comment, so how are you guys, we will
account, okay, Yoga Enroll
Contamination and 10100 phase, then its
price is ready, one and a half
Meghnad, okay, so this is the time change,
cash,
which has a completely different type of local, it has been fixed at
12304, this is
because I am, this is what happens, this is what happens, so
Its Panapur Gaya N0 12400 prevents it from moving in this direction
and it has
become
and the entrance has become more
and we subscribe to my channel due to which the
battery gets charged, our
mouth is scooter of ₹1, this is
Android car activated,
you people will have to see that, I will not
find it because it is electronic goods, so I will
read it, then at the time it will be very here, so
it did not open, this is the understanding, due to this it
burst from there, okay,
okay, something like this,
this game of yours, please okay, so if I
tell this, then its partner's
600-800 entry
dresses have been done, do
not forget to subscribe, if it is completed inside it, then
its heart will
soon be
completed and
50, so its use, so
now it is very good for me, in some places
it is very good, we should subscribe,
it was open, it does not stop,
I had seen that
donkey of Android, when we
change the oil in it, then this is on
top of it  It
went but it takes a lot of time, so I do
n't know much about it, but this is
not all, due to which
our scooter
gives very good mileage and sometimes it becomes
very good, has this happened or will it reach like this,
you people will get it completely,
I can tell you people, then
its price has become
only
0.0, you
can subscribe, I will bring it,
okay